jennsblahblahblog.com 2016-05-18

# Privacy Policy for Jenn's Blah Blah Blog

April 23, 2012 by 

This privacy policy sets out how Jenns Blah Blah Blog uses and protects any information that you give while using [www.jennsblahblahblog.com](http://www.jennsblahblahblog.com/)

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Jenns Blah Blah Blog  may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 11/7/2015.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, one of which is [http://www.gourmetads.com](http://www.gourmetads.com/). These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Newsletters**

If user opts-in to our newsletter mailing list they will receive emails with company updates, news, related product information, service information, etc.  If the user ever wishes to unsubscribe from our newsletter email list they can find detailed unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each email.  If user chooses they can contact us and we will remove them.  We use a third party provider to operate our business, the websites, and administer activities on our behalf, such has sending surveys or newsletters.  We may share your information with third parties for the purposes provided that the user has given their permission.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**Opt Out**

If you would like more information and to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If there are any changes to our Privacy Policy you will see those changes on this page

**Consent**

By using Jenns Blah Blah Blog you consent to our privacy policy.

**Contact Jenns Blah Blah Blog**

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at jennsblahblahblog@hotmail.com.

#### About Jenn

I have a smart mouth, don't sit still well, extremely opinionated, have a lot to say, work hard, love lots, love to smile and laugh, don't have time for drama, hurting people, or being negative, love animals, & my job as a New Mexico mom blogger! I love sharing travel adventures, tech gadgets, recipes, parenting struggles (success), crafts, helpful tips, giveaways and sweepstakes, product reviews, and more.  I have amazing 4 children, and am married my soul mate. When I'm not blogging, you'll find me spending time with my family, traveling, cooking, geeking out on tech, plotting the next home improvement, create crafts with the kids, and hang with my pitbull Skittles and newest bunny, Bun Bun. New Mexico born, moved all over, and meet my husband in Carlsbad, NM. We are plotting our move to greener pastures, with trees, and stuff. Connect with me on [Google + Page](https://plus.google.com/+Jennsblahblahbloggy/about).
